https://www.geappliances.ca/terms

Terms of Use
IMPORTANT NOTICE:
PLEASE READ CAREFULLY THESE TERMS OF USE BEFORE ACCESSING OR USING THIS WEBSITE. YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF THIS WEBSITE OR ANY OF ITS FEATURES, FUNCTIONALITY, USER INTERFACE, CONTENT OR CONTENT (COLLECTIVELY, THE “WEBSITE”) IS CONDITIONED ON YOUR FULL ACCEPTANCE OF AND COMPLIANCE WITH THESE TERMS OF USE. By using the Website, you indicate your agreement with these Terms of Use (the "Terms of Use") and the Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) and acknowledge that the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy will govern your access to and use of this Website.
Website Access. Permission to access and use the Website is conditioned upon your acceptance of these Terms of Use. Certain features and functionality may only be available after you successfully register to use such features and functionality. To successfully register to use such features and functionality, you must provide the information reasonably required by MC Commercial Inc. (“MC Commercial Inc.”) and indicated on the Website’s registration page (which information may include your name and email address).
Usage of Content; Rights Reserved by MC Commercial Inc.
All information, content, text, images, pictures, graphics, video, sound, streaming digital media and/or other information or data made available or accessed via this Website (collectively, the “Content”), and all associated rights, including copyrights and other intellectual property rights, are owned by MC Commercial Inc. You receive a limited, non-exclusive license to use this Website subject to these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy, but you do not acquire an ownership interest, contract right, intellectual property right or any other right to this Website or to the Content, in whole or in part. MC Commercial Inc. may terminate all rights and licenses contained herein.
By using this Website, you acknowledge that any product, process or technology comprised or described in this Website may be the subject of other intellectual property rights that are reserved by MC Commercial Inc. and are not licensed hereunder. The rights to all trade names, trademarks, logos or other expressions of brand identity of MC Commercial Inc. are expressly reserved hereby. Trademarks of other parties are identified wherever possible and MC Commercial Inc. acknowledges their rights.
The license in (a), above, is subject to the following restrictions: i) you must retain, on all copies of the Content downloaded, all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the Content; ii) you may not modify the Content in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose; iii) you may not transfer the Content to any other person without our written consent; and iv) you may not print or copy any of the HTML or other computer programs that are viewable at this Website. You agree to abide by all additional restrictions displayed on this Website as it may be updated from time to time.
Prohibited Use. You may not and shall not:
Grant access to, or allow any third party to gain access to your registration account for this Website;
License, sublicense, sell, resell, transfer, assign, distribute or otherwise commercially exploit or make available to any third party the Content in any way;
Modify or make derivative works based on the Content;
Use this Website to (i) send spam or unsolicited messages of any kind in violation of applicable laws; (ii) send or store infringing, obscene, threatening, libelous, or otherwise unlawful, tortious or objectionable material, including material harmful to children or violative of third-party privacy rights; (iii) send or store material containing software viruses, worms, or other harmful computer code, files, scripts, agents or programs; (iv) interfere with or disrupt the integrity or performance of this Website or the data contained therein;
Attempt to gain unauthorized access to this Website or its related systems or networks or otherwise interfere with the security of, or otherwise abuse, this Website or any services, system resources, accounts, servers or networks
connected to or accessible through this Website or affiliated or linked sites;
Reproduce, sell, publish, distribute, modify, display, translate, or make available any part of this Website as part of another website whether by hyperlink framing on the internet or otherwise;
Create any derivative works based on this Website or any component thereof;
Use this Website or its Content to construct a database of any kind; or
Distribute any database that contains or incorporates any part of this Website or Content.
In addition, you agree that you are solely responsible for actions and communications undertaken or transmitted in the course of your usage of this Website, and that you will comply with all laws that apply or may apply to your use of or activities on this Website or in respect of the Content. You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless each of MC Commercial Inc. , its affiliates, and each of their officers, directors, employees and agents, including all third parties mentioned at the Website, from and against any and all claims, actions or demands, including without limitation reasonable legal and accounting fees, alleging or resulting from your use of the Website and the Content or your breach of these Terms and Conditions.
On-line Communities and Other Interactive Areas. To the extent that this Website contains bulletin boards, chat rooms, or other message or communication facilities, you agree to use such forums only to send and receive messages and Content that are proper and related to the particular forum. By way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree that when using a forum, you will not post or otherwise disseminate on or through this Website harassing, defamatory, libellous, tortious, offensive, threatening, obscene or otherwise unlawful communications or Content of any kind, or Content which infringe or violate any third party's copyright, trademark, trade secrets, privacy or other proprietary or property right or that could constitute a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any applicable law; will not advertise or offer to sell or buy any goods or services for any commercial purpose unless such forum specifically allows such messages; will not conduct or forward surveys, contests, pyramid schemes or chain letters; and will not harvest or otherwise collect information about others, including e-mail addresses, without their consent. MC Commercial Inc. does not have any obligation to monitor the content of its bulletin boards, chat rooms, or other message or communication facilities. However, MC Commercial Inc. reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post and remove any information or Content, in whole or in part, that in MC Commercial Inc. 's sole discretion are objectionable or in violation of these Terms and Conditions.
DISCLAIMERS. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT USE OF THIS WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. NEITHER MC Commercial Inc., NOR ANY OF ITS EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, CONTENT PROVIDERS OR LICENSORS, MAKES ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, OF ANY KIND REGARDING THIS WEBSITE, THE CONTENT, ANY ADVERTISING MATERIAL, OR THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USE OF THIS WEBSITE. TO THE FULL EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, THE CONTENT IS PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN "AS IS" AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS FOR YOUR INTERNAL INFORMATIONAL USE ONLY, WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATION, CONDITION OR WARRANTY, INCLUDING OF ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF INFORMATION OR OTHER WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF QUALITY, MERCHANTABILITY, MERCHANTABLE QUALITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. MC Commercial Inc. WILL NOT BE LIABLE IN ANY RESPECT TO YOU OR TO ANY THIRD PARTY THAT MAY RECEIVE CONTENT FROM THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING FOR ANY DELAYS, INACCURACIES, ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE CONTENT OR IN THE TRANSMISSION OR FAILURE TO TRANSMIT ANY CONTENT, IN WHOLE OR IN PART. TO THE FULL EXTENT NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL MC Commercial Inc. BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES RESULTING FROM OR CAUSED BY A PARTY’S USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE OR A PARTY’S RELIANCE ON ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIAL ACCESSED VIA THIS WEBSITE OR ANY OTHER HYPERLINKED WEBSITE.
For clarity, the material on this Website may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors, and information may be changed, updated or deleted with or without notice. MC Commercial Inc. may make improvements and/or changes to the Content of this Website at any time. MC Commercial Inc. makes no warranties that this Website will operate uninterrupted or error free or that defects will be corrected. MC Commercial Inc. does not warrant that this Website is compatible with your computer equipment or that this Website or its server is free of errors or viruses, worms or "Trojan horses" and MC Commercial Inc. is not liable for any damage you may suffer as a result of such destructive features. You additionally acknowledge that this Website, and your access thereto may be subject to limitations, delays, and other problems inherent in the use of the internet and electronic communications. MC Commercial Inc. is not responsible for any delays, delivery failures, or other damage resulting from such problems.
For additional clarity, MC Commercial Inc. and its licensors make no representation, warranty, or guaranty as to the reliability, timeliness, quality, suitability, truth, availability, accuracy or completeness of the Website or of any Content.
Third Party Sites. MC Commercial Inc. does not endorse any websites that are or may be linked through this Website. MC Commercial Inc. may provide such links to you only as a matter of convenience, and in no event shall MC Commercial Inc. or its licensors be responsible for any content, products, or other Content on or available from such sites. MC Commercial Inc. makes no representations or warranties whatsoever about any other website that you may choose to access through this Website. Links provided by MC Commercial Inc. to such websites are provided solely for your convenience; such links do not constitute MC Commercial Inc.’s endorsement or approval of any other website or its content, and should not be relied on as such.
Changes to Terms of Use. MC Commercial Inc. reserves the right at its discretion to change these Terms of Use or the provisions of the Privacy Policy and will notify users of any such changes by posting such changes on this Website. Your continued use of this Website after the posting of any amended Terms of Use or amended Privacy Policy shall constitute your agreement to be bound by any such changes. MC Commercial Inc. may modify, suspend, discontinue or restrict the use of any portion of this Website, including the availability of any portion of the Content at any time, without notice or liability.
Governing Law and Exclusive Venue. These Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Canada and the Province of Ontario without regard to its conflicts of law provisions.
Language. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you have requested that this agreement and any related communication between MC Commercial Inc. and you be drawn up in the English language. Les parties aux présentes reconnaissent qu’elles ont exigé que la présente convention et tout document relié soit rédigés en anglais.
Questions. If you have any questions about these Terms of Use or about the Privacy Policy and MC Commercial Inc.’s collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information in connection with your use of the Website, please contact us as follows:
MC Commercial Inc.
Attention: Legal Department
Address: P.O. Box 5345, Burlington, Ontario, L7R 5B6
Email: Servicerequest@Mabe.Ca
Telephone: 1-888-561-3344
